WEB DEVELOPER

WILLIAM NJIE

404-680-1732 | Atlanta, GA | wsnjie@gmail.com https://wsnjie.github.io/portfolio/ | https://github.com/wsnjie

SUMMARY_

I am a full-stack web developer with a background in customer service and hospitality. Helping people is what motivates me, and I've got technical knowledge to find a solution. I have provided technical support both in-person and remotely for iOS and Mac devices which provided the opportunity to use technical knowledge to help others. I have also worked for 8 years as both a server and bartender. During that time I gained experience with time-management and team work, as well as written and verbal communication.

TECHNOLOGIES __

- HTML 5, CSS 3, Javascript, jQuery
- Node, Express, MongoDB
- React
- Python, Django, SQL
- Git and Github
- RESTful Routing
- Object Oriented Programming, Test-Driven Development, Responsive Design

EDUCATION —

GENERAL ASSEMBLY, 2018-2019

Web Development Immersive

MERCER UNIVERSITY, 2004 - 2008

next level. Link: https://wsnjie.github.io/simon-game/

Bachelor of Arts, Major in Biology

PROJECTS __

• Simon | A replication of the classic Simon game using HTML, CSS, and Javascript. Gameplay utilizes objectoriented programming to generate the CPU moves, recored the users moves, and advance the user to the

- Squad App | A schedule making app for users that allows them to create a schedule for a multi-day event and compare that schedule to other users. Link: https://evening-island-86988.herokuapp.com/
- FestPack | A packing list app that allows a user to create a packing list for an event, mark items that need to be purchased, and then mark of items they have packed. Link: https://fest-pack.herokuapp.com/

WORK EXPERIENCE __

STUDENT | GENERAL ASSEMBLY | 2018-2019

- 12 week Web Development Immersive
- Technologies focused in Git/Github, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node, MongoDB, SQL, Python, Django, etc.
- Completed individual projects combining frontend and back end technologies (detailed below)

APPLECARE IOS TECHNICAL SUPPORT TIER 1 | APPLE | 2018

- Technical support to 25-30 callers per shift
- position required some technical knowledge, each call presented different challenges and reaching a solution for the customer typically required some out-of-the-box thinking.

HOSPITALITY WORKER | 2009-2018

- 8 years combined experience at several Atlanta area restaurants as a server and bartender.
- Experience in small, chef driven concepts and high-volume restaurants
- Experience with menu development and staff training,

ENGLISH INSTRUCTOR | BRITISH BEAGLE CLUB | FUKUOKA, JAPAN | 2008-2009

- Individual and group English language instruction for Japanese students.
- Provided lessons to about 20 students each week
- Assisted with curriculum design of approximately 25 individual lesson plans